www.Richie-ee.com

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Professional Profile

Positive, passionate, reliable and persistent, individual who looks to make an impact on the world. Graduated Magna Cum Laude and continues learning new tools outside of work. Over 2 years of programming and familiar with multiple languages. Capable of working alone, but also communicates well in team environments.

Education

Master of Science in Computer Science, 2019 - Georgia Institute of Technology, Atlanta, GA *GPA: 4.0 Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering, 2014 - University of Central Florida, Orlando, FL *GPA: 3.8

Technical Skills

Languages: Java, C, HTML, CSS, Javascript, SQLite, Python, XML

Frameworks: Junit, Android, Picasso

Applications: Android Studio, Atom, Linux command line, GIT ➤ Education in Object oriented Design, Data structures, and Algorithms.

Software Portfolio/Classwork Highlights

Full list of projects available on www.Richie-ee.com

Cross-Site Request Forgery, Cross-site Scripting, and SQL Injection Attacks

- Intro to Information Security Spring 2017 Georgia Tech
- Bypassed Security defenses and crafted attacks the user would not suspect as malicious.
- Used HTML, Javascript, PHP, MYSQL in a virtual environment to attack a payroll website.

Movies Android Application

- Android application from Class in Udacity, updates user with Top and Recent Movies.
- Tools used: HTML requests, JSON, RecyclerView, Async Tasks, Picasso Framework, and theMoviesDB.org database.

Work Experience

Amped I LLC Chicago, IL

Electrical Engineer April 2015- April 2017

- > Worked under several teams of 2-5 engineers and for over 5 different clients.
- > Upgraded 12kv Feeders, fiber communication, and digital fault recorders.
- ➤ Helped start the drawing request intranet site using PHP, SQL, HTML, and CSS.

St. John's Optical Systems Sanford, FL

Electrical Engineer Intern Dec 2013- April 2015

- > Worked under senior Electrical Engineers and Physicists developing prototypes dealing with laser imaging and infrared products.
- Designed Printed Circuit boards, soldered, tested hardware and lasers.

University of Central Florida Orlando,FL

Research Assistant May 2013-Dec 2013

- > Aided graduate students in the research of Surface Acoustic Waves.
- > Prepared metal deposits and tested devices in the School's clean room.
- > Helped solder prototypes and create Graphical User interfaces in Matlab.

Professional References available upon request